之前在《星际迷航：下层甲板》...
Previously on Star Trek: Lower Decks...
MARINER: 哥们，又一个量子裂缝？
MARINER: Man, another quantum fissure?
BOIMLER: 你看到了那个其他的博伊默。
BOIMLER: You saw that other Boimler.
好酷且成功。
So cool and successful.
如果我模仿他，也许我也可以很酷。
If I copy him, then maybe I can be cool, too.
RUTHERFORD: 我的植入物正在
RUTHERFORD: My implant is having
连接这个旧门时遇到困难。
a hard time connecting to this old door.
好吧，也许我终于该填补
Well, maybe it's finally time I fill
高级科学官的职位了。
the senior science officer position.
你认为T'Lyn在和我竞争吗？
You don't think T'Lyn's competing with me, do you?
MARINER: 我刚听说你失去了船长职位，
MARINER: I just heard you lost your captaincy,
我会帮你拿回来。
and I'm gonna help you get it back.
MA'AH: 巴赫，我选你去死。
MA'AH: Bargh, I select you to die.
哦，太棒了，兄弟。
Ho, that was awesome, brother.
我们一直假设这些维度裂缝
We've been assuming these dimensional rifts
是自然现象，但现在看起来
are a natural occurrence, but now it's looking
像是有人在制造它们。
like someone's making them.
你经历过复制吗？
You have experienced duplication?
我的意思是，如果他还在，我敢打赌他会
I mean, if he were still around, I bet he'd be
在某个巨大的冒险中。
in some huge adventure.
- 哈利，你必须停止。 - [咯咯笑]
- Harry, you have to stop. - [cackles]
斯洛恩：通过定向孤子爆发，我可以引导
SLOANE: With a directed soliton burst, I can guide
波浪进入一个单一的现实。
the wave into a single reality.
水手：整个宇宙不会被摧毁吗？
MARINER: Won't an entire universe be destroyed?
使用我的现实。
Use my reality.
我将消息转发给我的复制品。
I piggybacked a message to my duplicate.
- 他会知道该怎么做。 - 他会吗？
- He'll know what to do. - Will he?
威廉：是的，只要他不崩溃。
WILLIAM: Yeah, as long as he doesn't freak out.
我们的扫描是负面的。
Our scans are negative.
该地区没有敌人。
There are no enemies in the area.
雷尔加：我可以看到。设定航向边界。
RELGA: I can see that. Set course for the border.
也许我们可以激怒星际舰队来打仗。
Maybe we can antagonize Starfleet into a fight.
但高级委员会认为他们是盟友。
But the High Council considers them to be allies.
[嘟] 委员会！
[bleep] the council!
我们只是在这个毫无价值的帝国角落巡逻，
We're only patrolling this worthless corner of the empire
因为我的兄弟们被谋杀
because my brothers were murdered
而委员会认为我软弱！
and the council thinks me weak!
我宁愿割掉他们所有的喉咙，也要有机会...
I would cut all their throats for a chance to...
舰长，传感器正在检测到泰克粒子的增加。
Captain, sensors are detecting an increase in tachyons.
泰克粒子对猛禽号毫无意义。
Tachyons mean nothing to a Bird-of-Prey.
[笑声]
[laughter]
嗯？
Huh?
我正在读到大量的孤立子粒子累积。
I'm reading a massive buildup of soliton particles.
快把我们带离这里！
Get us out of here!
- [喊] - [尖叫]
- [shouts] - [screaming]
[用力]
[straining]
我们已经躲过孤立波，
We have evaded the soliton wave,
但克尔塔斯已经被摧毁。
but the Krtas has been destroyed.
- 我应该向指挥部报告吗？ - 不。
- Shall I report this to command? - No.
这正是我需要的。
This is exactly what I needed.
[笑]
[laughing]
赎金：第一官员的日志。
RANSOM: First officer's log.
在一个星际舰队-克林贡研究站完成修理后，
Having finished repairs at a joint
塞里托斯号正在享受一些待命时间。
Starfleet-Klingon research station,
内容：
the Cerritos is enjoying a little downtime.
啊。因为我们下午都放假，
Ah. Since we both have the afternoon off,
想在全息甲板上玩性感宝藏岛吗？
want to play Sexy Treasure Island on the holodeck?
只有在我可以成为长约翰[消音]的情况下。
Only if I get to be Long John [bleep].
- 天啊，我爱你。 - [轻声笑]
- God, I love you. - [laughs softly]
啊，成为准尉真是太好了。
Ah, being a lieutenant JG rules.
谁知道更高的军衔带来了更多的玩乐自由？
Who knew higher rank came with more freedom to goof around?
这真的很放松。
It's honestly very relaxing.
我第一次到来时你可不是这样的态度。
That was not your attitude when I first arrived.
你更混乱。
You were more chaotic.
真的吗？啊。可不想失去我的优势。
Really? Ah. Don't want to lose my edge.
- 享受那个牛油果，学员！ - [喊]
- Enjoy that avocado, cadet! - [shouts]
[轻笑] 还行。
[chuckles] Still got it.
你们在忙什么？
What are you guys so busy with?
高级科学官的事务。
Senior science officer stuff.
我在编目可波普尔水平
I am cataloging the corbopple levels
- 的等角法兰计。 - 而我在研究
- of the isometric flangometer. - And I'm researching
可波普尔排放如何影响睡眠。
how corbopple emissions affect sleep.
可-可波普尔-- 你在开玩笑。这不真实。
C-Corbopple-- you're messing with me. That's not real.
- 一半的波普尔都是被可波的。 - 它是
- Half of all bopples are corbed. - It is a foundational element
- 人工引力的基础元素。 - [grunt]
- of artificial gravity. - [grunts]
- [呻吟] - 拉瑟福德。
- [groans] - Rutherford.
我一直在尝试修理这个愚蠢的老等离子路由器，
I've been trying to fix this stupid old plasma router,
这对于我的植入物应该很简单，
which should be easy with my implant,
但塞里托斯的系统太旧了。
but the Cerritos systems are too old.
你爱塞里托斯。别听他的，女孩。
You love the Cerritos. Don't listen to him, girl.
- 他不是那个意思。 - 是的，我是。
- He didn't mean it. - Yes, I did.
[叹气] 从什么时候开始大家都把工作带到酒吧？
[sighs] Since when does everyone bring work to the bar?
我希望我能帮助你，拉瑟福德，
I wish I could help you, Rutherford,
但我从这个我从另维度偷来的PADD上
but there's not a lot of engineering advice
没有多少工程建议。
on this PADD I stole from alt-dimension me.
我无法相信以那个东西为基础
I cannot believe basing your personality
来塑造你的个性居然真的管用。
on that thing actually worked.
那个胡子看起来不错。我讨厌它。
That beard looks good. I hate it.
我其实并没有抄得那么多。
I didn't actually crib all that much.
嗯哼。你想喝点什么？
Uh-huh. What do you want to drink?
呃，呃，叫做布兰布尔的东西？
Uh, uh, something called a Bramble?
[设备发出嗶嗶声]
[device beeping]
你收到了消息，博伊姆斯。
You're getting a message, Boims.
威廉：不，不，一定有我们可以做的事。
WILLIAM: No, th-there has to be something we can do.
马里纳：难道你不是要让整个宇宙都毁灭吗？
MARINER: Won't you be dooming an entire universe?
威廉：扫描我。使用我的现实。
WILLIAM: Scan me. Use my reality.
你为什么要这样对你的朋友？
Why would you do this to your friends?
抱歉，复制器没有布兰布的代码……
Sorry, the replicator didn't have a code for a Bramb...
天啊，我们都要死了！
Holy [bleep], we're all gonna die!
什么-什么鬼？博伊姆斯，等一下！我们在尖叫什么？
What-what the hell? Boims, wait up! What are we screaming about?
- [博伊姆尔在远处尖叫] - [玻璃破碎]
- [Boimler screaming in distance] - [glass shattering]
是我一个人这样，还是博伊姆尔
Is it just me, or is Boimler
总是对一些PADD感到恐慌？
always freaking out about some PADD?
- 不止是你。 - [咕咕声]
- It is not just you. - [grunts]
[金属碰撞声]
[metal clatters]
弗里曼：塔波尔？哈里·金姆？
FREEMAN: T'Pol? Harry Kims?
一个跨维度的过载？
An interdimensional overload?
船长，如果威廉还活着，他不会在这方面撒谎。
Captain, if William's alive, he wouldn't lie about this.
妈妈，我知道这来得很突然
Mom, I know this is coming from nowhere
而且我们只是初级军官，
and we're just junior officers,
但我们必须认真对待。
but we have to take it seriously.
- 我同意。 - 哦。你真这么想？
- I agree. - Oh. You do?
- 现在就让指挥部来联系。 - 哇，真的？
- Let's get Command on the line now. - Whoa, what, really?
我是说，我们以为需要更多的说服力。
I mean, we thought it would take way more convincing.
是啊，我是说，一个不死的传输克隆
Yeah, I mean, an-an undead transporter clone
可能有点牵强。
could be kind of a stretch.
你们两个是我最好的官员。
You two are my best officers.
毕竟我们经历的一切，
And after all we've been through,
我想我足够了解可以信任你。
I think I know enough to trust you.
哇。我是说，谢谢。
Wow. I mean, thanks.
伙计，那真是个好船长。
Man, that is good captaining.
[马’啊抱怨]
[Ma'ah grumbling]
哎，为什么这么紧张，兄弟？
Eh, why so tense, brother?
我们还有几个小时才能到达Qo'noS。
We still have hours before we arrive at Qo'noS.
船长必须保持警惕。
A captain must be vigilant.
我们送来血酒。我们会遇到什么危险？
We deliver bloodwine. What danger would we encounter?
一个漏水的桶？
A leaky barrel?
- 每个任务都是一场潜在的战斗。- [哈欠]
- Every mission is a potential battle. - [yawns]
如果卡赫利斯再次出现就叫我。
Wake me if Kahless makes another appearance.
- [警报响起] - [喊]
- [alarm blares] - [shouts]
[倒吸气]
[gasps]
- [尖叫] - 马’啊：雷尔加。
- [screeching] - MA'AH: Relga.
啊，伟大的马’啊船长，运送垃圾。
Ah, the great Captain Ma'ah, hauling garbage.
这不是垃圾。是酒！
It's not garbage. It's wine!
强者如何堕落，谋杀者。
How the mighty have fallen, murderer.
这是什么意思？
What is the meaning of this?
你毁掉了我的一艘船。我很幸运能活下来。
You destroyed one of my ships. I was lucky to survive.
我们不知道你在说什么。
We don't know what you're talking about.
我知道，但有足够的真相
I know, but there's just enough truth
来说服高级委员会。
to convince the High Council.
准备武器。
Ready weapons.
- 这太疯狂了！ - 不，这是报复。
- This is madness! - No, it's vengeance.
瑞尔加没有荣誉，就像她的兄弟们一样。
Relga has no honor, just like her brothers.
巴赫和多尔格很弱。我不是！
Bargh and Dorg were weak. I am not!
开火！
Fire!
[咕哝声]
[grunts]
- [咕哝声] - [抽泣声]
- [grunts] - [whimpers]
我会撞毁他们的桥。
I will ram their bridge.
我们将拥有突然袭击的机会。
We will have the element of surprise.
抱歉，兄弟，但今天不是个好死的日子。
Sorry, brother, but today is not a good day to die.
[咕哝声]
[grunts]
马阿：你在做什么？
MA'AH: What are you doing?
现在解锁我的控制！马洛！
Unlock my controls now! Malor!
远程扫描已经证实了你的担忧，自由人舰长。
Long-range scans have confirmed your fears, Captain Freeman.
孤立波共振正在超载维度裂缝。
Soliton resonance is overloading the dimensional rift.
如果不加以控制，这将摧毁我们的量子现实。
Unchecked, this will destroy our quantum reality.
[所有人倒吸一口气]
[all gasp]
裂缝本身可以用亚空间胶子束轻松密封。
The rift itself is easily sealed with a subspace gluonic beam.
问题在于如何到达那里。
The problem is getting to it.
裂缝被围绕着
The rift is surrounded
一个薛定谔可能性场。
by a Schroödinger possibility field.
什么？
A what?
S场完全重新映射物质
The S-field completely remaps matter
到多元宇宙中的其他可能性。
into other possibilities from the multiverse.
- [所有人倒吸一口气] - T'LYN: 迷人。
- [all gasp] - T'LYN: Fascinating.
当然，我们永远不会选择让一艘加州级船
Of course, we would never choose to have a California-class ship
处理如此规模的灾难。
handle a catastrophe of this scale.
哦，感谢上帝。
Oh, thank God.
一瞬间，听起来这完全由我们决定。
For a moment, it sounded like this was up to us.
不幸的是，是的。
Unfortunately, it is.
什么？！为什么？
What?! Why?
企业号正在前往，但没有时间了。
Enterprise is en route, but there's no time.
两个博伊默尔以我们尚未理解的方式相连。
The two Boimlers are linked in ways we don't yet understand.
称其为命运或纠缠，这就是你的使命。
Call it fate or entanglement, this is your mission.
我们该怎么做这个，天哪
How the hell are we supposed to do this
如果我们的头变成了仙人掌？
if our heads are turning into cactuses?
我已经计算了你们护盾谐波的调整。
I've calculated adjustments for your shield harmonics.
理论上，它们应该可以阻挡场的影响。
In theory, they should block the effects of the field.
现在发送它们。
Sending them now.
“理论上”？
"In theory"?
工程部可以进行这些更新，舰长，
Engineering can make these updates, Captain,
但我们必须全天候工作。
but we'll have to work around the clock.
如果它们真的有效，那就太好了。
It'd be nice to know if they actually work.
来吧。你确定企业号应付不了这个？
Come on. Are you sure the Enterprise can't handle this?
有了连接的博伊莫尔，你是我们唯一的选择。
With the connected Boimlers, you're our only option.
什么[咕哝]? 你把一个毁灭宇宙的裂缝
What the [bleep]? You sent a universe-destroying rift
发送到你自己的维度？
to your own dimension?
不是我。是威廉！
It wasn't me. It was William!
看来博伊莫尔没有给我们选择。
Looks like the Boimlers have given us no choice.
- [大家 groan] - 大家快点。
- [all groan] - Let's move, people.
来吧！是威廉！
Come on! It was William!
梅瑞迪斯：我们得安裝那些更新。
MEREDITH: We got to get those updates installed.
[grunt]
[grunts]
这些等离子导管是古老的。
These plasma conduits are ancient.
我们永远无法及时冲洗它们。
We're never gonna flush them in time.
我的植入物可以快两倍地做到这一点
My implant could do this twice as fast
如果我们不必使用历史上最古老的中继器。
if we didn't have to use history's oldest relays.
明白了。
Got it.
量子过滤正在进行中。
Quantum filtering is live.
防护罩已更新，舰长，
Shields are updated, Captain,
但我认为星际舰队没有考虑到船体。
but I don't think Starfleet took into account the hull.
弗里曼 [通过通信]: 什么？你什么意思？
FREEMAN [over comm]: What? What do you mean?
似乎存在潜在的干扰
There seems to be a potential interference
场与铀钛合金之间
between the field and the duranium alloys
遍布整艘塞里托斯号。
throughout the Cerritos.
这可能会影响船体，
It could affect the hull,
但防护罩的更新应该确保
but the shield updates should make sure
船员不受影响，所以我们都会没事！
that the crew is unaffected, so we'll all be fine!
船体是很重要的。
The hull is kind of important.
比卢普斯: 我们正在修复。
BILLUPS: We're working on a fix.
- 我们只需要更多时间。- 好吧，时间很紧迫。
- We just need more time. - Well, time's in short supply.
但只要没有任何复杂情况，我们就应该没问题。
But we should be okay as long as there aren't any complications.
[警报声响起]
[alert blares]
舰长，一艘小飞船刚刚脱离跃迁。
Captain, a small vessel just dropped out of warp.
他们在呼唤我们。
They're hailing us.
该死。屏幕上。
Damn it. On screen.
我们需要和贝基特·马里纳谈谈。
We need to talk to Beckett Mariner.
[两人都在 grunt]
[both grunting]
她是我家族的家族。
She is my cha'DIch's cha'DIch.
我们请求庇护。
We are requesting asylum.
呃…是的，嘿，大家，时机有点不对。
Uh... yeah, hey, guys, sort of bad timing.
好的。我不想申请庇护。
Good. I do not want asylum.
- 是的，你要的！ - 啊，我才不要！
- Yes, you do! - Ugh, I do not!
是的，我不知道他们在说什么。
Yeah, I don't know what they're talking about.
[呻吟] 那我想我们最好去弄清楚。
[groans] Then I guess we'd better find out.
马洛尔：哦，来吧。
MALOR: Oh, come on.
我们离瑞尔加还远着呢，当她的船受到损坏时。
We were nowhere near Relga when her ship was damaged.
他们可能遇到了相同的孤子波。
They probably encountered the same soliton wave
我们正在处理。
we're dealing with.
瑞尔加因我杀了她的兄弟而寻求复仇。
Relga seeks revenge because I killed her brothers.
呃，好的，让我插一句。
Uh, yeah, let me just hop in here.
这两个家伙都先想杀了他。
Both of those guys tried to kill him first.
我会高兴地在战斗中面对她而死！
I will gladly die facing her in battle!
来吧，她永远不会给你一个公平的战斗！
Come on, she will never give you a fair fight!
我们可以给他们安全的避风港，对吧，妈妈？
We can give them safe harbor, right, Mom?
是的，但限制在船舱内。
Yes, but confined to quarters.
抱歉，但显然，我们是唯一可以
Sorry, but apparently, we're the only ones
拯救今天这个该死的宇宙的人。
who can save the frickin' universe today.
那么，这些船舱，嗯，有复制器吗？
So, do these quarters, um, have a replicator?
你是怎么在战斗后还有食欲的？
How do you have an appetite after running from battle?
我们所有的零食都是用虫子做的。
All our snacks are made of bugs.
他们有咸味和甜味的！
They have salties and sweets!
RANSOM：船长，我们需要你在舰桥上。
RANSOM: Captain, we need you on the bridge.
更多的克林贡刚刚脱离了超空间。
More Klingons just dropped out of warp.
- 什么？ - 好。
- What? - Good.
我们没有时间处理这个。
We don't have time for this.
我们本该在闭合一个裂口。
We're supposed to be closing a rift.
显示屏。
On screen.
我想你是Relga？
I'm assuming you're Relga?
我已追踪到两个谋杀犯在这个地点。
I have tracked two murderers to this location.
现在把他们交出来！
Hand them over now!
我相信我们可以以外交方式解决这个问题。
I'm sure we can solve this in a diplomatic fashion.
你在庇护罪犯。
You are harboring criminals.
他们会不同意。
They would disagree.
我知道你是谁，船长卡罗尔·弗里曼。
I know who you are, Captain Carol Freeman.
你的海军上将伙伴不会保护你免受我的侵害。
Your admiral mate will not protect you from me.
我丈夫与此事无关。
My husband has nothing to do with this.
你和破坏我船的petaQs站在了一起。
You've sided with the petaQs who destroyed my ship.
你是同谋吗？
Are you an accomplice?
来自弗里曼海军上将的来电，船长。
Incoming call from Admiral Freeman, Captain.
[叹气] 现在怎么了？
[sighs] What now?
好的。让她保持通话。
Okay. Put her on hold.
没有人能让我保持通话...
Nobody puts me on hol...
弗里曼：佐...
FREEMAN: Zo...
我们部分更新了我们的护盾，
we've partially updated our shields,
我们应该能够前往裂缝...
and we should be able to head to the rift...
你在庇护两个罪犯克林贡，船长。
You're harboring two criminal Klingons, Captain.
[笑] 消息传得真快。
[chuckles] Word travels fast.
我不相信他们犯了任何罪。
I don't believe they've committed any crime.
他们是谋杀犯。我命令你
They're murderers. I'm ordering you
立即将他们交给雷尔加船长。
to immediately hand them over to Captain Relga.
爸爸，这些是我的朋友。
Dad, these are my friends.
这是来自指挥部的通知吗？
Is this coming from Command?
佐，我...
Zo, I...
- 这很奇怪。 - 今天整天都很奇怪！
- That was weird. - This whole day is weird!
[叹气] 兰萨姆，收集我们的客人。
[sighs] Ransom, collect our guests.
什么？不！这是[哔]。
What? No! This is [bleep].
我们不能仅仅因为涉及朋友就制定自己的规则。
We can't make our own rules just because friends are involved.
给我那个克林贡。
Get me that Klingon.
富里曼！你会后悔那一天...
Freeman! You will rue the day...
够了！你得到了你想要的。
Enough! You're getting what you want.
啊，他来了。
Ah, there he is.
不再逃跑，懦夫。
No more running, coward.
- 你才是懦夫！ - 等等。
- You are the coward! - Wait.
胖子在哪里？
Where's the fat one?
兰萨姆，为什么我只有一个克林贡？
Ransom, why do I only have one Klingon?
兰萨姆：正在处理。马洛似乎已经，呃，
RANSOM: Working on it. Malor seems to have, uh,
- 走开了。 - 好的。
- wandered off. - Good.
这是一个把戏。
This is a trick.
传感器找不到他。我有一个团队在船上搜索。
Sensors can't locate him. I have a team sweeping the ship.
请耐心等待。
Please be patient.
我们实际上正在处理一个危险的裂缝
We're actually dealing with a dangerous rift
正在释放奇怪的能量。
that's emitting strange energy.
作为盟友，我给你发送数据
As allies, I'm sending you the data
关于如何更新你的护盾。
on how to update your shields.
我对这个没有用！
I have no use for this!
把两个兄弟都给我们，否则我会强行带走他们！
Give us both brothers or I will take them by force!
- [大家喘息] - 胡'tegh！
- [all gasp] - Hu'tegh!
- 他们瞄准了我们的引擎！ - 红色警报！
- They're targeting our engines! - Red alert!
SHAXS: 护盾在80%。
SHAXS: Shields at 80%.
机动规避！
Evasive maneuvers!
设定前往裂缝的航线。
Set a course for the rift.
- 但是，舰长... - 我们没有时间打斗。
- But, Captain... - We don't have time for a fight.
让我进入曲速。
Warp me.
我需要关于那些护盾更新的好消息，比卢普斯先生。
I need good news on those shield updates, Mr. Billups.
那些克林贡人离我们肯定不远。
Those Klingons can't be far behind.
比卢普斯: 正在处理。
BILLUPS: Working on it.
- 妈，我没有藏马洛尔。 - 弗里曼: 我知道。
- Mom, I didn't hide Malor. - FREEMAN: I know.
但我仍然需要你现在找到他。
But I still need you to find him now.
那些克林贡人正在把我们逼入一种糟糕的境地。
Those Klingons are forcing us into a bad situation.
博伊姆勒: 我们正在接近薛定谔场。
BOIMLER: We're approaching the Schroödinger field.
舰长，如果没有护盾更新，
Captain, without the shield update,
将会对船体产生量子干扰
quantum interference with the hull
可能改变塞里托斯的物理结构。
could alter the physical structure of the Cerritos.
好吧，不管我们变成什么
Well, whatever we turn into
总比被克林贡人炸毁要好。
is still better than getting blown up by Klingons.
全速推进。
Full impulse.
是，船长。
Aye, Captain.
赎金：孤子能量与铝合金反应。
RANSOM: Soliton energy's reacting with the duranium.
读数变得奇怪！
Readings are getting freaky!
全员，准备迎接怪异情况。
All hands, brace for weird.
- 报告。 - 我们只有一个推进器。
- Report. - We only have one nacelle.
我们在一个塞里托斯的现实中，
We're in the Cerritos from a reality
那里是自由级。
where it's a Freedom-class.
你怎么能用一个推进器进入超光速？
How do you even go to warp with one nacelle?
在没有双推进器的情况下投射一个超光速气泡是可能的。
It's possible to project a warp bubble without dual nacelles.
唯一的牺牲是静态执行器……
The only sacrifice is the static actuators...
我们没有时间对此进行详细讨论，中尉。
We don't have time to nerd out about this, Lieutenant.
- [警报响起] - 我们的朋友们刚刚赶上。
- [alert rings] - Our friends just caught up.
当然，他们赶上了。
Of course they did.
保持速度。我们必须到达那个裂缝。
Maintain speed. We have to get to that rift.
谢克斯：克林贡人已经进入S场，船长，
SHAXS: The Klingons have entered the S-field, Captain,
我们的护盾只达到了60%。
and our shields are only at 60%.
另一股能量波，正前方。
Another energy wave, dead ahead.
- 马洛尔：马洛尔！- 海员：马洛尔！
- MA'AH: Malor! - MARINER: Malor!
现在就出来，让我们面对敌人。
Get out here right now so we can face our enemies.
你不这样做吗？你会吓到他的。
Would you not? You're gonna scare him.
- [飞船轰鸣] - [两人惊呼]
- [ship rumbling] - [both exclaiming]
马洛尔，拜托——可不可以出来，马洛尔？
Malor, just-- c-could you get out here, please, Malor?
哇！
Whoa!
该死！愚蠢的新量子现实能量中继器。
Dang it! Stupid new quantum reality power relays.
- 移植问题？- 不，它工作得很好。
- Implant trouble? - No, it's working great.
但这些新系统一团糟。
But these new systems are a mess.
谁设计的这种飞船？
Who designs a ship like this?
- [爆炸] - 啊！
- [explosion] - Ah!
他们的其中一艘飞船正在改变。
One of their ships is changing.
哇，一艘古老的克林贡帆船。
Oof, an ancient Klingon sailing barge.
所有生命都失去了。
All lives lost.
那会发生在我们身上吗？
Can that happen to us?
我真的很需要那个护盾升级，比绥尔先生。
I could really use that shield update, Mr. Billups.
博伊默中尉，去导航。
Lieutenant Boimler, get to navigation.
我们不能偏离航线。
We can't afford to go off course.
[通过公共广播系统]：全体人员到达各自岗位。
[over P.A.]: All hands to your stations.
我们需要更新我们的中继器。
We need to update our relays.
塞里托斯号并不是为这种压力设计的。
The Cerritos wasn't designed for this kind of stress.
我们需要禁用非必要系统
We need to disable nonessential systems
以帮助为结构完整性导入电力。
to help route power to structural integrity.
负面。禁用系统可能会损坏资源通道。
Negative. Disabling systems could damage resource conduits.
是的，如果我们被炸了，资源流就不重要了！
Yeah, resource flow won't matter if we get blown up!
提高音量无法解决问题。
Raising your voice will not solve the problem.
什么也不做也同样无济于事！
Neither will doing nothing!
我们是共同的高级科学官。
We are co-senior science officers.
我们应该一起处理这个问题！
We should be working together on this!
看来我们状况的压力
It appears the pressure of our situation
- 正在影响你的逻辑。- [倒吸气]
- is impairing your logic. - [gasps]
也许我们应该处理不同的系统。
Perhaps we should work on different systems.
也许我们应该。
Perhaps we should.
[咕哝，踢]
[grunting, kicking]
我无法让任何一条绝缘线中继器稳定。
I can't get any of the isolinear relays stabilized.
是这艘船。我...
It's this ship. I...
我想我对塞里托斯号的爱正在减弱。
I think I'm falling out of love with the Cerritos.
什么？但还有很多需要修复的地方。
What? But there's so much more to fix.
也许这只是一个艰难的阶段。
Maybe this is just a rough patch.
我就是这么想的。
That's what I thought.
但是情况就是没有好转。
But it just isn't getting better.
- MARINER: Malor? - 这太不光彩了！现在就出来！
- MARINER: Malor? - This is dishonorable! Get out here now!
Malor？嘿，Kimolu，Matt，
Malor? Hey, Kimolu, Matt,
你看见一个乡村克林贡从这里进来吗？
you see a rural Klingon come in through here?
唔！如果我能找到他，我们就可以停止这场冲突。
Ugh! If I could only find him, we could stop this conflict.
等一下。我知道我用这个PADD太多了，
Wait. I know I use this PADD too much,
但是也许像这样的事情发生过
but maybe something like this happened
在Beard Boimler的现实中。
in Beard Boimler's reality.
你知道吗？老实说，我会接受任何帮助。
You know what? Honestly, I'll take any help.
检查，检查。
Check, check.
- MA'AH: Malor! Malor! - 哇。
- MA'AH: Malor! Malor! - Whoa.
你是真的找到什么了吗？
You actually found something?
这是一本关于克林贡寻求庇护的日志。
It's a log about Klingons seeking asylum.
- Becky Mariner是藏匿他们的人。- 什么？！
- Becky Mariner is the one who hid them. - What?!
哇，这并不意味着我做了。
Whoa, that doesn't mean I did.
- 她是个麻烦人物。- 我弟弟在哪里？
- She was a piece of work. - Where is my brother?
- 我没有藏他。- 这里说你藏了！
- I didn't hide him. - This says you did!
揭露他的所在地！
Reveal his location!
- 伙计们，伙计们，我们能专注于修理吗？- [ grunt ]
- Guys, guys, can we focus on repairs? - [grunts]
- [轰鸣声] - BOIMLER: 哇。
- [rumbling] - BOIMLER: Whoa.
小心。我们又要改变了。
Look out. We're changing again.
塞里托斯号现在是一艘地球帝国舰船。
The Cerritos is a Terran Empire ship now.
啊，真是神明保佑，我们的武器真棒！
Ah, by the prophets, our weapons are amazing!
哦！武器失效了。啊！
Oh! Weapons are down. Aah!
瑞尔佳，请理智一点。
Relga, please be reasonable.
这个区域本身就很危险。
This field is dangerous as it is.
你本不该给我盾牌更新的，人类。
You never should have given me the shield updates, human.
现在把那些逃犯交出来！
Now hand over those fugitives!
[叫喊，喘息]
[exclaiming, grunting]
告诉我我们还有护盾。
Tell me we still have shields.
勉强有，但引擎失效了。
Barely, but engines are down.
我们在太空中死了。
We're dead in space.
FREEMAN: 我不明白。
FREEMAN: I don't get it.
她的船为什么不变化？
Why isn't her ship changing?
她可能在变化。
It probably is.
克林贡人几乎从不更新他们的舰队设计。
Klingons hardly ever update their fleet designs.
他们总是想让他们的船看起来像大愚蠢的鸟。
They always want their ships to look like big stupid birds.
我们有基本的动力系统，但就只是这些。
We have basic power systems, but that's it.
我的团队仍在努力修复干扰，
My team's still working to fix interference,
但这让我们更加落后。
but this set us back even more.
我们必须假设我们会被登船。
We have to assume we'll be boarded.
在这种情况下，我认为我们必须交出那个...
In that case, I think we have to hand over the...
- 弗里曼船长！ - [惊叫]
- Captain Freeman! - [exclaims]
这个紫色小子有证据证明马里纳隐藏了我的兄弟。
This purple boy has proof that Mariner has hidden my brother.
妈妈，我不会对你撒谎。
Mom, I wouldn't lie to you.
我是说，你知道的，不再撒谎了。
I mean, you know, not anymore.
我知道。我信任你。
I know. I trust you.
马洛尔的所在位置隐藏在这个设备的某个地方。
Malor's location is hidden somewhere on this device.
- [ grunt ] - 把PADD给我！
- [grunts] - Give me the PADD!
[ grunt ]
[grunts]
- 巴卡！ - 博伊姆斯，那东西是为你工作的。
- Ba-Qa'! - Boims, that thing was working for you.
你真帅又酷。
You're so handsome and cool.
如果意味着不支持你，我不想让它出现在我的生活中。
I don't want it in my life if it means not having your back.
哦，伙计，那实际上-- 真的是太甜了。
Oh, man, that's actually-- That's really sweet.
你是比胡子博伊姆尔更好的朋友。
You're a better friend than Beard Boimler.
我不需要PADD来知道这一点。
I don't need a PADD to know that.
- 友谊！ - 马阿：不！
- Friendship! - MA'AH: No!
如果你不告诉我马洛尔在哪里，
If you will not tell me where Malor is,
我就要在战斗中让你告诉我！
I will have to make you, in battle!
[咆哮]
[growling]
[痛苦的 grunt] 你怎么这么强？
[pained grunt] How a-are you s-so strong?
高强度间歇训练。
High intensity interval training.
这已经太过分了。
This has gone too far.
- 我藏了马洛。 - 什么？
- I hid Malor. - What?
- 哈！我[屏蔽]早就知道了。 - 为啥？
- Ha! I [bleep] knew it. - Why?
弗里曼海军上将的那条消息让我觉得不对劲。
That message from Admiral Freeman didn't sit right.
是的。谢谢你。妈妈，听起来不像爸爸。
Yes. Thank you. Mom, it did not sound like Dad.
我们答应了马洛庇护，雷尔加是个恶霸。
We promised Malor asylum, and Relga's a bully.
我知道你必须遵循命令，
I knew you had to follow orders,
所以我给了你时间和一点可信的否认。
so I bought you time and some plausible deniability.
那不是你的决定，杰克。
That wasn't your call, Jack.
乌赞尼，当光线照射过山峰时。
Uzani, when the light came over the mountain.
我们不需要看这个。他的命令是明确的。
We don't need to watch this. His orders were clear.
金扎，当真相被揭露时。
Jinza, when the truth was uncovered.
他们是杀人犯。我命令你立即把他们交出来……
They're murderers. I'm ordering you to immediately hand them...
啊，她伪造了消息。
Ah, she faked the message.
该死。这真是不光彩。
Damn. That is so dishonorable.
我们不能把他们交出去，但我们也不能反击。
We can't hand them over, but we can't fight back.
[叹气] 这是一个不可能的局面。
[sighs] This is an impossible situation.
我不敢相信我们有特兰武器
I can't believe we have Terran weapons
但没有办法为它们供电。
and no way to power them.
必须有一些狡猾的下三滥科克式把戏
There has to be some sneaky underhanded Kirk-style trick
我们可以用来搞砸她，就像他们在以前那样。
we can use to [bleep] her up, like they did in the old days.
[倒吸气]我的一个军官可能能帮忙。
[gasps] One of my officers might be able to help with that.
你真的要让我登上你的船吗？
Are you really going to make me board you?
拯救一些生命。不要这么软弱。
Save some lives. Don't be so weak.
好吧，至少我不用假装发一条消息。
Well, at least I didn't have to fake a message.
什么？[ chuckles ]
What? [chuckles]
可惜你发现了我的把戏。
A pity you discovered my trick.
现在你的船员必须死！
Now your crew has to die!
你知道吗，你说得对。
You know, you were right.
我真的不应该分享那个护盾更新。
I really shouldn't have shared that shield update.
我想我就只能把它拿走。
Guess I'll just have to take it away.
我想看看你怎么尝试。
I'd like to see you try.
[雷声轰鸣]
[thunder crashing]
[用力]
[straining]
开火！
Open fire!
[喊]
[shouts]
有效了！我做到了，比卢普斯先生！
It worked! I did it, Mr. Billups!
哈！你的小把戏根本没用！
Ha! Your little trick did nothing!
舰长，我们的护盾失效了。
Captain, our shields are down.
我们完全暴露在能量场中。
We are fully exposed to the energy field.
什么？不。
What? No.
攻击他们！摧毁他们！
Fire on them! Destroy them!
[尖叫]
[screaming]
[呻吟]
[groaning]
[喉音尖叫]
[guttural screams]
[低吼]
[snarling]
[咆哮]
[roars]
呃。他们正在变成什么？
Ugh. What are they turning into?
无意识的原始克林贡，充满愤怒。
Mindless proto-Klingons, filled with rage.
[咆哮]
[roars]
- [警报声] - 波频率正在上升，舰长。
- [alarm beeps] - Wave frequency is increasing, Captain.
全体成员，准备迎接撞击。
All hands, brace for impact.
[吸气]
[gasps]
舰长，塞里托斯号正在运行。
Captain, the Cerritos is operational.
我们已经完全变成了主权级。
We've gone all Sovereign-class.
我想我得接管它。
I guess I'll have to take it.
指挥官，带我们去裂缝。
Helm, get us to the rift.
我们越接近，影响就会越大。
The closer we get, the more the effects will increase.
那么就希望我们能到达。
Then let's hope we make it.
全速前进！
Full impulse!
嘿！我们回到正常了。
Hey! We're back to normal.
是的，我们是。
Yeah, we are.
[喘气] 我们是！
[gasps] We are!
舰长，裂缝扩展得太快了。
Captain, the rift is expanding too quickly.
我们不会及时到达的！
We won't get there in time!
为什么我们不能换成一艘更大、更好的船？
Why couldn't we have changed into a bigger, better ship?
拉萨福德 [通过通讯]: 没有更好的船！
RUTHERFORD [over comm]: There is no better ship!
- 拉萨福德？ - 加利级船是最棒的！
- Rutherford? - The Cali-class rules!
我们对此非常合适。[ grunt ]
We're perfect for this. [grunts]
田迪：但我以为你不再爱了。
TENDI: But I thought you were falling out of love.
是的，但我后来意识到
Yeah, but then I realized
我的问题不在于塞里托斯。
my problems aren't with the Cerritos.
而在于我的植入物。
They're with my implant.
[ grunt ]
[grunts]
是时候采用老派的方法了。
Time to do this the old-fashioned way.
[ grunt ] 这些 计算机 是 被 设计 的
[grunts] These Calis were designed
为了 所有 种类 的 功能。
for all sorts of functionality.
我们 可以 重新配置 系统 比 任何人 都好。
We can reconfigure systems better than anyone.
哇！ 我从未见过有人 这么快 地 工程。
Whoa! I've never seen someone engineer that fast.
[ chanting ]： 拉塞福德！ 拉塞福德！
[chanting]: Rutherford! Rutherford!
- 拉塞福德！ 拉塞福德！ - [ beeping ]
- Rutherford! Rutherford! - [beeping]
他 正在 将 裂缝 的 能量
He's routing the rift's energy
直接 输入 到 费米箱 里。
directly into the dilithium chamber.
我们 正在 被 异维度性 本身 供能。
We are being fueled by interdimensionality itself.
结果 将 会 是 不可预测 的。
The results will be unpredictable.
这 将 是 必须的。
It'll have to do.
- [ 所有 gasp ] - [ echo ]： 发生 了 什么？
- [all gasp] - [echoes]: What's happening?
我们的 超位置 正在 解耦！
Our superpositions are decoupling!
弗里曼： 塞里托斯 正 在 分叉 成 两个 量子 可能性。
FREEMAN: The Cerritos is bifurcating into two quantum possibilities.
如果 我们 维持 这个 速度， 它们 都会 被 毁灭。
If we maintain this speed, they'll both be destroyed.
我们 没有 选择。
We don't have a choice.
保持 我们 的 方向， 博伊姆勒 先生。
Keep us on course, Mr. Boimler.
在 尝试， 船长，但 驾驶室 不 在 响应。
Trying, Captain, but the helm's not responding.
沙克斯： 系统 已 经 分裂。
SHAXS: Systems are split.
[ 喊 ] 每艘 舰船 正在 控制 另一艘。
[yelps] Each ship is controlling the other.
赎金：我们必须减慢速度。
RANSOM: We have to slow down.
- 不！- 不！
- No! - No!
今天的混乱使我们分开了。
Today's chaos has driven us apart.
但那是我们最需要同步的时候。
But that's when we need to be the most in sync.
放弃控制。互相信任。
Relinquish control. Trust each other.
之前，我们必须证明自己。
Before, we had to prove ourselves.
现在我们团结为...
Now we unite as...
- 科学好朋友。- 科学好朋友！
- Science besties. - Science besties!
什么...？
Wha...?
[小组发出咕哝声]
[group grunts]
[喘气] 兄弟？
[pants] Brother?
[小组尖叫]
[group screams]
赎金：舰长，我们在范围内！
RANSOM: Captain, we're in range!
激活胶子束。
Active the gluonic beam.
没效果。
It's not working.
[警报响起]
[alarm rings]
腾迪：裂缝仍然开放。
TENDI: The rift is still open.
太迟了！
It's too late!
在我的农场...
On my farm...
- 嗯？- 什么？- ...当一条河流威胁
- Huh? - What? - ...when a river threatens
摧毁你的庄稼，
to destroy your crops,
你无法阻止它，但你可以建一个水坝。
you cannot stop it, but you can build a dam.
- 你在说什么？ - [倒抽气] 他是对的。
- What are you talking about? - [gasps] He's right.
[咕哝]
[grunts]
[嗡嗡声]
[whirring]
BOIMLER: 哇，能量被隔离了。
BOIMLER: Whoa, the energy's contained.
裂缝是稳定的，但它，呃，
The rift is stable, but it's, uh,
- 它是永久开放的。 - 天哪 [哔]。
- it's permanently open. - Holy [bleep].
等一下，我们刚刚拯救了 [哔] 宇宙？
Wait, did we just save the [bleep] universe?
[欢呼]
[cheering]
嗯？ 我们胜利了，因为你听了马洛尔的？
Huh? We are victorious because you listened to Malor?
是的。估计兰索姆做了一个正确的决定
Yeah. Guess Ransom made a good call
藏起这个大天才，否则我们就完蛋了。
hiding this big old genius, or we'd be toast.
[咕哝] 克林贡人不拥抱。
[grunts] Klingons do not hug.
- [笑] - 闭嘴。
- [laughs] - Shut up.
BOIMLER: 博伊姆勒的日志。
BOIMLER: Boimler's log.
我们的克林贡朋友正在返回 Qo'noS，
Our Klingon friends are heading back to Qo'noS,
但他们可能没有时间耕种。
but they might not have time for farming.
由于她的不光彩行为，
Due to her dishonorable actions,
最高委员会移交了瑞尔加的舰队
the High Council handed over Relga's fleet
听从马阿赫的命令。
to Ma'ah's command.
现在裂缝已成为一个永久开放的传送门。
Now that the rift is a permanently open portal
到其他量子现实，
to other quantum realities,
星际舰队将其视为通往全新前沿的大门。
Starfleet considers it a gate to a whole new frontier.
增强的超光速粒子密度意味着没有现代星际基地
The increased tachyon density means no modern starbase
可以驻扎在附近。
can be stationed nearby.
幸运的是，有一个较旧的系统没有受到影响。
Luckily, there's one with older systems that aren't affected.
星基地80.
Starbase 80.
使命：探索奇异的新现实
The mission: explore strange new realities
在一些熟悉的朋友的帮助下。
with a little help from some familiar friends.
卡西亚仍然在管理基地。
Kassia still runs the base,
但是当涉及到探索多元宇宙时，
but when it comes to exploring the multiverse,
星际舰队希望他们的最佳选择
Starfleet wanted their best
监督进入裂缝的任务。
to supervise the missions going into the rift.
[轻声喵喵]
[meows softly]
这是我的荣幸，舰长。
It's been an honor, Captain.
[哼哼，费力]
[grunts, strains]
- [抽泣] - [呻吟]
- [sniffles] - [groans]
如果你不在这里，谁来把我扔进监禁室？
If you're not here, who's gonna throw me in the brig?
当你第一次到达时，
When you first arrived,
我没想到你能坚持一周。
I didn't think you'd last a week.
是的，我也没想到。
Yeah, neither did I.
- [咕哝] - 现在
- [grunts] - Now
我自豪地说你不需要我了。
I'm proud to say that you don't need me.
轮到我去冒险了。
It's my turn to go on an adventure.
[抽泣]
[sniffles]
- 我爱你，妈妈。 - 我也爱你。
- I love you, Mom. - I love you, too.
难道没有人来帮我提包吗？
Is nobody here to carry my bags?
是的，这不是银河级，爸爸。
Yeah, it's not a Galaxy-class, Dad.
- 但我是一名海军上将。 - 那又怎样，你的手臂不工作吗？
- But I'm an admiral. - So what, your arms don't work?
我很高兴你们能一起多花些时间。
I'm glad you guys get to spend more time together.
这就是我同意这个的主要原因。
It's the main reason I agreed to this.
- 有高尔夫球场吗？ - 哦，忘了高尔夫。
- There's a golf course, right? - Oh, forget golf.
你正在去健身房，伙计。
You're hitting the gym, buddy.
[笑]: 不，谢谢。不适合我。
[laughs]: No, thank you. Not for me.
弗里曼：好吧，你可是每天都在给我打电话，
FREEMAN: Well, you're the one who was calling me every day,
非常想念我。
missing me so much.
这不是你想要的吗？
Isn't this what you wanted?
我爱你，但我也爱放置。
I love you, but I also love putting.
欢迎来到星际基地80，弗里曼斯。
Welcome to Starbase 80, Freemans.
现在让我们来给你涂抹滑滑的东西
Now let's get you slimed up
用一些自制的消毒凝胶。
with some homemade disinfectant gel.
- 她是在开玩笑，对吧？ - [笑] 你希望如此。
- She's kidding, right? - [laughs] You wish.
哦，拉瑟福德。嘿，你能看一下
Oh, Rutherford. Hey, will you take a look
我为--什么？编制的数据吗？
at this data I compiled for-- what?
你的植入物在哪里？
Where's your implant?
我不得不在塞里托斯和眼罩之间选择。
I had to choose between the Cerritos and the oculus.
根本谈不上选择。
Not really a choice at all.
呃，我，我，我不知道该说什么。
Uh, I-I, I-I don't know what to say.
工程学现在应该有两倍的趣味
Engineering should be twice as interesting
毕竟我没有网络连接
now that I don't have cybernetics
接入我的大脑。
hooked up to my melon.
不过，感觉如此有机确实很奇怪。
It does feel weird to be so organic, though.
- 呸。 - 我觉得你看起来非常英俊。
- Bleh. - I think you look very handsome.
哦！谢谢，滕迪。哇。[笑]
Oh! Thanks, Tendi. Wow. [laughs]
情感可能会变得相当强烈
Emotions can get pretty intense
没有多巴胺抑制剂，是吧？
without a dopamine inhibitor, huh?
- [轻笑] 哦。- 我不知道你有浪漫情感。
- [chuckles] Ooh. - I was unaware of your romantic affection.
哦，不，我们只是朋友。
Oh, no, we're just friends.
- 我的头感觉热。 - 什么？
- My head feels hot. - What?
- 我生病了吗？ - 让我给你量一下体温。
- Am I sick? - Let me take your temperature.
[拉伸，尖叫]
[strains, shrieks]
显然我错了。
Clearly I was mistaken.
[ grunt，轻笑]
[grunts, chuckles]
[叹气] 今天真糟糕。
[sighs] What a day.
伙计，谁决定在星际飞船上设一个酒吧的？
Man, whoever decided to put a bar on a starship
值得一枚奖牌。
deserves a medal.
马里纳，快点，你妈妈要离开塞里托斯了。
Mariner, come on, your mom's leaving the Cerritos.
我们预测你会表现出负面反应。
We had predicted you would express a negative reaction
不符合您等级的身份。
unfitting to the station of your rank.
你知道博伊姆勒那个奇怪的假死克隆体为什么吗？
You know why Boimler's weird death-faking clone
那个宇宙波是发给我们的吗？
sent that cosmic wave at us?
因为他知道我们表现出色。
Because he knew we kick ass.
而我说的并不只是我们五个人。
And I'm not just talking about the five of us.
整个塞里托斯号的船员汇聚了了不起的军官。
The whole Cerritos crew is stacked with amazing officers.
是的，舰队中有很多更大的船。
Yeah, there's a lot of ships in the fleet which are bigger,
更花哨，他们有工程部分。
fancier, they have engineering sections
附在船的主要部分上的那些东西。
that are attached to the main part of the ship.
老实说，那些船员要专业得多。
And honestly, those crews are way more professional.
嘿，我应该知道，我已经被开除过一半。
Hey, I should know, I've been kicked out of half of 'em.
但我们做的这件事不需要完美。
But this thing we do doesn't require perfection.
我们是探险者。我们为未知而生。
We're explorers. We live for the unknown.
你无法为此做准备。
You can't prepare for that.
在塞里托斯号上没有人接近完美。
Nobody on the Cerritos is even close to perfect.
我们是一群人和各种生物的混合体，
We're a mishmash of people and various creatures
在其他地方都无法融入。
that don't fit in anywhere else.
但我们是一家人。
But we're a family.
这就是我爱这里的原因。
That's why I love it here.
我们相信使命，相信彼此。
We believe in the mission and in each other.
我妈妈可能已经离开，
My mom might be gone,
但她亲自挑选了这个船员。
but she handpicked this crew.
这就是我知道我们会没事的原因。
Which is why I know we're gonna be okay.
这不是故事的结束，而是开始。
This isn't the end of the story, it's the beginning.
我们会让她感到骄傲。
We're gonna make her proud.
哇，这真是一种健康的看待方式。
Wow, that's such a healthy way of looking at it.
是啊。我确实生气了，还把我的床点着了。
Yeah. I did get mad and set my bed on fire.
- 等等，什么？ - 什么？！还在烧吗？
- Wait, what? - What?! Is it still burning?!
是的，我踢了一台计算机，但是你知道，
Yeah, and I kicked a computer, but you know,
这已全部出系统。我很好，我想。
that's all out of my system. I'm good, I think.
我--我是说，我不知道。我们得等着看。
I m-- I mean, I don't know. We'll have to wait and see.
[笑] 调整频道。哦哦。
[chuckles] Tune in. Uh-oh.
SHAXS: 舰长在甲板上。
SHAXS: Captain on deck.
弗里曼舰长在80号星际基地上，
Captain Freeman's aboard Starbase 80,
- 朗萨姆舰长。- 谢谢你，沙克斯先生。
- Captain Ransom. - Thank you, Mr. Shaxs.
你知道，她告诉我永远不要让你引爆曲速核心。
You know, she told me to never let you detonate the warp core.
哦，天哪。
Oh, man.
- 除非你真的值得。- 好的！
- Unless you really deserve it. - All right!
拉瑟福德先生，有小鸟告诉我
Mr. Rutherford, a little birdie told me
你对等离子注射器进行了相当有启发性的更新。
you made some pretty inspired updates to the plasma injectors.
是米格利莫博士吗？
Was it Dr. Migleemo?
是的，是的。继续保持良好的工作。
Yes, it was. Keep up the good work.
- 好的。- 星际舰队想让我们
- Okey dokey. - Starfleet wants us
去看看在斯尼克米克5号上的一些会说话的胶状物。
to check out some talking goo on Snickmik 5.
那胶状物的粘度是多少？
What viscosity is the goo?
哦，它有什么好说的吗？
Ooh, does it have anything nice to say?
让我们找出来。
Let's find out.
舰长，请让我们出发。
Helm, take us out.
嘿，杰克。呃，我是说，舰长。
Hey, Jack. Uh, I mean, Captain.
这会成为一个问题吗？
Is this gonna be a problem?
不，你是塞里托斯坚强的。
Nah, you're Cerritos strong.
博伊姆勒，跟我们聚在一起。
Boimler, huddle up with us.
聚在一起？哦，不，我们不做教练对话。
Huddle up? Oh, no, we're not doing coach talk.
我需要一个执行官。
I need a first officer.
[倒吸气] 但我只是一个初级中尉。
[gasps] Bu-- uh, but I'm only a lieutenant JG.
[轻声笑] 我知道你还没有完全准备好，
[chuckles] I know you're not quite ready,
但你们俩有机会让它成功
but the two of you have a chance of making it work
作为临时执行官。
as provisional first officers.
什么？
What?
- 那不算事。 - 现在算了。
- That's not a thing. - It is now.
我可能最终会提升你们中的一个。
I might eventually promote one of you.
- 把它当作一个比赛。 - 请不要这样做。
- Think of it as a contest. - Please don't do this.
这会破坏我们的友谊。
It will mess up our friendship.
嗯，一点人际冲突
Eh, a little interpersonal conflict's
是学习的最佳方式。
the best way to learn.
- 自从什么时候？ - 先生，但我，我不能。
- Since when? - Sir, but I-I can't.
我不——我们还是低甲板。
I don't-- we're still lower decks.
不，你负责低甲板。
No, you're in charge of the lower decks.
找个座位。
Grab a seat.
[呜咽] 哦，天啊。
[whimpers] Oh, man.
[呻吟]
[groans]
兰萨姆：哦，
RANSOM: Oh,
我得想出一个酷炫的东西
I got to figure out a cool thing
在我们进入曲速时说。
to say when we go to warp.
我——我觉得这会自然发生，随着时间的推移。
I-I think it'll happen naturally, over time.
是啊，你不想听起来像是强迫的。
Yeah, you don't want it to sound forced.
哦，我想到了一个。启动引擎。
Ooh, I got one. Engage the core.
- 呃，不。我不喜欢。 - 不，不。你敢
- Uh, no. I don't like it. - No, no. Don't you dare
- 在锻炼笑话上进入曲速。 - 不，我很抱歉，
- go to warp on a workout joke. - Nope, I'm sorry,
- 我喜欢。就这样。 - 兰萨姆，你比这更优秀。
- I like it. It's staying. - Ransom, you are better than this.
博伊姆勒：不，请不要让我们的生活变成这样，先生。
BOIMLER: No, please don't make this our lives, sir.
玛丽纳：来吧，你不想定下这个基调。
MARINER: Come on, you don't want to set that tone.
- 博伊姆勒：先生...... - 如果这是一个五年任务呢？
- BOIMLER: Sir... - What if this is a five-year mission?
- 兰萨姆：启动引擎！ - [玛丽纳和博伊姆勒呻吟]
- RANSOM: Engage the core! - [Mariner and Boimler groan]
由WGBH媒体访问小组提供字幕，访问wgbh.org
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
[男子模仿武器开火]
[man imitates weapons firing]
唧唧。
Chirp.